Episode 6                    First Date?
Rin! I need to grab some tools!
Come on in!
Hey, a sailor uniform!
It looks cute on you. Maybe you
should try transferring schools.
That's not really a casual thing to try!
Good point.
And if you changed schools,
I wouldn't get to see your acting anymore.
Still, the idea of being reunited at work
after a few years... That'd be pretty cool too.
No matter where I go,
I promise to keep acting!
That way, we'll be reunited soon!
Rin...
I'll show you an even
better performance someday!
So...
So... please, don't forget about me.
Uh, Senpai?! I was just acting! Acting.
I know, but...!
I started thinking about you
actually changing schools, and...
I didn't realize how sad it'd make me!
It's okay. I'm not going anywhere.
Why are you so happy about that?
Even if we're separated,
I'll never forget you.
So, let's see each other
again once we're grown up...
Underneath the promise tree!
I really can't focus like this...
What else can we do?
The prop isn't finished.
Don't mind me!
"Once we're grown up," I said.
That was quite a vague promise to make.
It's been five years...
I'm here again, now that I'm 20, but...
Will he show up?
The line is "That man."
Um... could the tree please not talk?
That man would never break his promise...
And they do say women mature faster.
Maybe to him, 20 years old
isn't grown up yet?
Just like a tree...
We're both still children... really...
Quit treating me like a kid!
I can't take this anymore!
It's now been fifteen years.
Surely 30 years old must be grown up.
Wait, doesn't the next scene involve
me crying and clinging to this tree?!
Where could he be..? Why isn't he here?
Uh... er...
Bring it in, come on!
Dang it, Eiji! Quit talking!
I can't do this in front of other people...
Maybe if we were alone...
Come to think of it, this was a lucky
chance to see your acting up close!
If only we were alone!
Good morning.
Good morn—
Are you recording already?
Well, yeah!
I'm getting the inside
scoop on our lead actress.
Now
recording
Making-Of
Interview!
Now
recording
Making-Of
Interview!
This'll be one more thing to put on
display for the culture festival.
What does acting mean to you, Nanakura-san?
Isn't it early for that question?!
Shoot... I can't think of any questions...
Uh...
Did you watch that show yesterday?
Sweatpants Detective.
Is... that your interview question?
I didn't think to prepare any!
Let's continue this during lunch.
To the cafeteria!
O-Okay!
This comprehensive coverage is awesome!
Ginger-Fried Pork Lunch
I'll get you one of the same, cameraman.
Kitahama's
Documentary
Actress
Nanakura Rin
"Before a big performance,
leading woman Nanakura Rin
always comes here
for the ginger-fried pork."
That sounded pretty authentic!
Do you actually do that, though?
Not really, no...
I get to eat with Senpai! Lunch with Senpai!
How do you feel when you've landed
the leading role in a production?
So much fun!
You have fun with it?
Er, no! I-I was talking
about something else!
Time to eat!
I'm not sure a staple food like
ginger-fried pork would suit
the palate of a princess
like Tsundere-chan...
I usually don't eat this sort of thing...
I-It seems fine, I guess!
I think I'm going to hold onto this
footage for my personal collection.
Please erase it!
Also, should we be
fooling around like this?
Crud, we don't have much time!
Do you have any thoughts as the star?
Make it a good one!
Well...
I honestly don't think of
it in terms of being a lead.
A production is always a group effort,
and I just try to do my best for my part.
I'd say. Maybe.
What's wrong, Senpai?
The battery!
Oh, come on!
I'm so sorry!
So, will the coverage be
continuing after school?
Do you mind?
But you have to take it seriously this time!
Yes!
Man, I've never spent a night at school.
The night before an event
is always so exciting.
I got so excited I volunteered
for the shopping team, but then
I realized I still had a bunch
of other stuff I hadn't finished...
That's not good.
Anyway, what do you wanna do about dinner?
Well, maybe some bento boxes...
Hey, look! The beef is on sale!
Sale! 30% Off!
Maybe we could whip up some sukiyaki!
Except we can't use any gas...
But it's a special occasion!
That means we should eat special food!
Rin, is there anything you want?
I'm good with anything.
That's the hardest response
to work with, y'know.
Japanese? Western? Chinese?
Japanese food, then!
Then we gotta do sukiyaki, after all!
Having to put thought into food
takes more effort than I imagined...
If we get married, would we be
doing stuff like this every day?
Are you... talking about... with me?
Would you be willing to make
sukiyaki for me every day?
That's... honestly asking too much.
What's up?
Uh... bathroom... can't go...
There are other students around!
you don't need to be so scared.
What about getting into
a character who's less afraid?
I get the feeling Cool-chan
might actually enjoy spooky stuff.
Ghosts... I like... ghosts...
That's just regular Rin-chan!
Don't be! Don't be! Afraid!
Rin-chan's a strong girl! She's just fine!
Totally fine!
After the night comes the dawn!
As it should be! There we go!
D-don't... d-don't be...
don't don't be... afraid!
I... I can't go!
You've got this, Rin-chan!
Pseudo
Harem
Please wait right here, okay?!
Pseudo Harem
Kouban
Private
High
School
64th
Cultural
Festival
Fried Chicken
Iced
Coffee
Ice Cream
Song Intro Quiz
I wanna go around the culture
festival with Senpai...
So tired!
Oh, Senpai!
Are you all done setting up the stage?
Not even close!
Next is the non-stop round trips
where I bring in all the tiny parts.
I'll help out, then.
Don't be ridiculous.
Backstage stuff is our job.
You need to focus on your performance.
Okay.
Here.
I bought it on my way back.
Thank you!
All right, I gotta go.
Okay!
Takoyaki
Frankfurters
Kouban Festival
Hey, Rin, you around?
I grabbed these on the way back.
All of that?
Hey, Rin!
Rin! Check out this stuff they were selling!
Rin!
Senpai, this isn't fair!
I-I just wanted to give you
a taste of the festival,
since you don't get to walk around...
Then I want to help set up, too!
Hey, I finally found you.
Almost time for the show.
I'm feeling a little nervous.
Hey, I know...
If you do a good job acting,
I'll give you a reward.
A reward?!
Reward?!
Oh, but then I really need
to get it right...
Good point.
In that case, how about you
get a reward either way?
Are you okay with that?
I realize it makes no sense, but sure.
In that case...
I want to go on a date with you, Senpai.
A date?!
I-I didn't get to go around
the culture festival at all!
So, y'know...
Oh man, now I'm feeling nervous too!
A date! A date! Where should we go?
The aquarium might be nice!
Aquarium
Look there, Rin! What a cutie.
Even cuter than me?
Oh, you spoiled girl!
I think maybe we'll just stick to shopping!
I wonder where...
Senpai would like to go?
Kyoto
K-Kyoto?!
I managed to snag two tickets to a musical.
Kinda like a class trip, huh?
Kyoraku Theater
Are you that excited for the musical?
Oh... no,
I was just thinking it really
is like going on a class trip.
In that case, we should do
some more class trip stuff.
Good idea!
I guess that'd include pillow fights...
That always comes to mind
when traveling with groups.
Don't you agree, Imp-chan?
It'd be boring if we didn't stay
the night, is that it?
Whoa! You almost had me hollering!
Does Tsundere-chan mind heights?
N-Not really. This isn't scary at all...
But you'd better not push me!
Is this that thing where you keep
going "Don't do it! Don't do it, man!"?
It's not a bit!
How can you even suggest that?!
I was just joking.
This is perfect scenery for Demure-chan.
The humble surroundings still give you a
feel for this ancient city's air of elegance.
Onii-chan, I want dango!
Seven servings, please!
This again?
What souvenirs should we get?
I bet Cool-chan would love this sensu fan.
See?! Perfect!
I'll take good care of it.
Hey, what do I get?
I'd say Spoiled-chan gets this
kinchaku bag with the cat pattern!
I wanted to get the Japanese sweets instead!
It's still got a cat on it!
Kyoto Souvenirs Kikuya
That said, getting the run-around
from Spoiled-chan feels appropriate.
Maybe that is the right choice...?
It was a good idea, coming together.
So, what about you, Rin?
I...
I'd be happy no matter what I get, I think.
Not that. I mean, are you
enjoying our little trip together?
Definitely!
Pick something out for me, too.
You, Senpai...
This!
Y-You nailed it!
Day Trip
Onsen Baths
Senpai, I bought some drinks.
He fell asleep...
W-What's going on here?
I... want to stay with you forever, Senpai.
Rin...
C-Could you... f-forget
about what I just said?!
I just got out of the bath,
so my hair is still a mess,
and my head's not sorted out, so...
That's why...
I want to have another
chance to do it right!
Okay.
I really do love him, though!
This place is gorgeous, huh?
I-It sure is, yup.
Yup?
What do I do? I can't talk properly!
The cobblestones are kinda
tough to walk on, so be careful.
I'm too embarrassed to even face him!
Rin!
Maybe we should just hold hands?
I can't do this!
It's not easy for me, either!
Why not?!
Hey... good morning.
Kinda cold today, huh?
We better be careful not to get sick, huh?
Yes...
It'd be nice to go on another trip,
huh, Tsundere-chan?
Well... I thought it might
make it easier for you to talk.
Since I want to talk with you, Rin.
N-Next time, I get to decide where we go!
Sounds nice! Where's
Tsundere-chan want to go?
...C-cat cafe...
But aren't the cats are gonna be
hanging off your twintails?
That's obviously not going to happen!
I'll see you at club, then.
Senpai!
Hiss!